Thank you for watching!
Uncle Nogisaka
Hi there, this is Nogisaka no Ojimyu!
I'm Bananaman, your host, and it's nice to meet you.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Messiah Galle
Are you wearing an apron?
I don't know. Some people wear aprons.
And some without.
I wonder...
Mr. Kimura, let's hear today's plan.
The "Late-night Mecicero Queen" competition!
Tonight, instead of elaborate dishes, we'll introduce the ultimate nighttime meal that the members are proud of and can easily prepare.
Five people entered in each of the two categories.
Bananaman and the members will decide the queen of late-night meals!
You know, Ume put a lot of effort into this project.
He put a lot of effort into this project.
We got a lot of responses to our questionnaire and a lot of people wrote that the food looked delicious.
We got a lot of responses.
We put out as much as we could.
I've got a lot of late-night delicacies.
Yes, we do.
It's very strong.
It's just, you know, in the past, you know, that cooking project...
Shokichi... he's a piece of garbage.
Even though I still have that feeling...
Why are you entering today?
I thought you wouldn't find out...
Of course they will, I ate it!
I mean, did you have that late-night gourmet thing in the first place?
Or did you just rush into this project?
It's like a special project.
I wrote this and it just happened to get accepted.
Well, it's true that the last time I did that project, it was sudden.
It was sudden.
Maybe that's why I couldn't do it.
You have a solid recipe to begin with.
Yes, I do.
What about the peas?
What about the garden?
For temperate cuisine?
You drink alcohol with it, don't you?
It's a good snack.
If I write about it...
I don't know.
But... even if you like to drink, you don't eat snacks.
I wonder which side you're on... the "quick and easy" or the "tasty" side.
You've never taught me anything.
Shhh...
First, let's face off in the late-night easy snacks category!
First up is Kubo
Kubo, what are you going to make?
I'm going to make Kubo's dumplings!
Yes, yes!
Hey, you know what?
I didn't bring it to the party!
That's right
That's great, I wanted to eat it!
No...
I love dumplings!
It's not cheesy... everyone loves dumplings.
No, but we do a lot of research when it comes to gyoza.
No... not the usual ones.
Not at all.
Oh, yeah.
We've done a lot of research.
What if they're not gyoza anymore, but shumai?
I've done a lot of research.
It's too ultimate.
Okay, then, Mr. Himura, Mr. Himura in the kitchen.
Ah!
Cute.
So cute!
Here they come. They weren't aligned at all.
The camera guy lowered it.
Come on, Yuuno-san, Yuuno-san!
Here it comes!
Please pay attention for once
Now, now, this is Mr. Kubo making Hakuoboke's dumplings
Yes, look at the picture below, it's finished!
Yes, we'll make two of them this time.
Yes, I'm going to wrap two pieces this time.
I'm going to wrap a couple of them, but I'm particular about the skin.
I'm particular about the skin.
I like the skin so much, I won't tell you.
I love it so much I won't tell you.
It's a store-bought one?
It's a regular store-bought skin like this.
You make the folds like this.
How do you make the folds?
Yes, I'm used to it.
I'm used to making them.
What kind of dumplings does the Kubo family use?
Kubo family uses Chinese cabbage.
We are particular about it. We blanch the Chinese cabbage with salt to drain off the water.
The water is drained out, but the water is not discarded and the meat is put in the watery state.
It's not watery at all, it's just a little bit dry.
The skin that I am particular about is the skin that traps all the juices, so it's very important for me to keep it moist.
So the ratio of meat to Chinese cabbage is more Chinese cabbage or more Chinese cabbage.
More Chinese cabbage.
I didn't actually put garlic in this time, so there's plenty of vegetables, so even if you eat it this late at night, it won't linger for the next day.
Wait a minute, what is this fat?
It's sesame oil.
Sesame oil is very strong, isn't it?
It's difficult to cook dumplings well, isn't it?
Here's the point... you add water, but I use hot water.
But I use hot water.
It's pretty fast.
Don't you put it in after frying the surface?
No, I steam them first, and then put them in right away.
Hot water
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Was it hot?
It's time to wait for a while.
Yes, we're on a bit of a waiting period.
What song would you like me to sing for you?
What is your favorite musician?
I listen to Mr. Koji Tamaki.
Mr. Tamaki?
The part about Mine Red.
You're not going to sing it, are you?
You're not going to sing this?
All of it.
While we're waiting...
I usually freeze these.
I always keep them in the house.
I come home at night.
I just bake it, so it only takes like five minutes or something.
Oh, great.
I can freeze them in a jiffy.
So when you're hungry, you can have a little bit of it and snack on it.
Come on, Mr. Hittle.
Yes, yes, yes.
The dumplings will be ready soon.
Here we go, open!
Here you go.
Yes, yes, yes.
Turn up the heat a little at a stretch here to let the water drain off.
Brown them here.
Browning here.
Finally, you brown it again, right?
I'm going to brown it here.
Looks good, looks good, looks good.
Two, two.
I like it.
Shiori's dumplings, too.
I see.
Yes, I've had them before.
And Shiori's homemade salted bread?
Salted bread is good, too.
I've had it before.
You can't go wrong with her cooking.
It's so good!
Delicious!
Come on, Mr. Hittle.
Yes, yes, yes.
Here it comes, here it comes, on a plate!
A plate, all at once.
This one.
Boom!
Oh, wow.
It's done.
Finished.
Finished
Title.
Kubo Family Dumpling
A good one
It's good!
First of all, they really look like restaurant dumplings!
I'm so happy!
A little bigger than usual!
Be careful, the gravy is quite thick!
First of all...
Here...
Yum!
I'm so happy!
Oh, my God!
It's just as juicy as I said it would be.
It's so juicy and juicy!
Oh, it's so good!
Thank you so much.
Oh, isn't that the winner?
I'm so happy!
Oh, my God!
Yum!
Congratulations on these dumplings!
There's soup in there.
By adding watery Chinese cabbage in the soup, it's not too greasy.
so you can eat a lot of dumplings.
This is super delicious!
I'm so happy, I'm so happy!
Is this the first time you've had it, except for Yamamoto?
It's my first time.
Isn't it good?
It's so good!
You don't even need soy sauce to taste it.
I want to eat it with rice now.
Wow!
This is seriously one of the best dumplings I've ever had.
This is good too!
This is going to win the showbiz dumpling championship.
Really? I'm so happy!
I wish they'd do something like that on TV.
I'm so happy!
What was the next late-night snack brought by Ioki?
Toro Toro Tomato Box.
What? Toro Toro Tomato Box?
Do you eat this often?
When I was in junior high school, I was so hungry after club activities.
I was looking for something in the fridge.
I thought it would be delicious with this and that.
So this is your original menu?
Yes, it is.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll be looking forward to it.
Have a good day!
First, I'll cut the tomatoes.
What?
And then we'll cut a little bit of the buttocks.
It will stand up like this.
And then hollow out the inside.
I'm going to be a little aggressive with this one.
Be careful.
You're going to cut it out.
You're holding it like this.
He was holding it like this.
It's the way Chucky used to hold it.
Then he put butter and mixed cheese in the tomatoes.
I don't see any other ingredients in my hand yet.
What's this?
This is mozzarella cheese.
Mozzarella!
If you don't have any mozzarella in the fridge, just use what you have.
I see.
Then there's something I've been into lately.
What's that?
Well...
There it is!
It's "holinish".
The "horinishi"! Horinishi!
That's great!
It's a legendary all-purpose seasoning developed by an outdoorsman!
This is it!
After seasoning the tomatoes with holinish, put them back in the tomatoes.
Then, put it back in the tomatoes, sprinkle some more oi cheese on it, and heat it in the microwave at 600 watts for 1 minute.
Now, Mr. Himura, it's time for your one-minute show, what would you like to sing?
Let's hear your favorite musician.
A musician?
Who do you listen to a lot?
Mrs. Green Apple
Mrs. Greenapple!
Dan! Dan!
Something's wrong.
Mrs. Green Apple!
Musician!
You don't know Mrs. Green Apple's music.
Mini-Hewesas!
You're allowed to know the name Mini-Hewesas Green Apple.
No, no, no.
Great.
Sara, you were all done.
I bet.
Yes, look.
Let me show you what kind of images we have.
Deliver them.
Ta-da!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Here we go again oihorinishi!
Oihorinishi!
This is the most destructive holinish I've ever seen.
That's right.
It's really good!
And to finish it off, basil and tomato caps!
Ioki's tomato box is complete!
Yes, it's done!
Now, I'm ready to serve Ioki's dish!
The aroma is Italian, what you would call tomato and cheese.
The aroma is Italian, what you would call tomato and cheese, but the holinish is spicy.
And the fresh basil is a nice touch.
It's hot!
This is a very hot dish.
The juice is absolutely hot.
Oh, man!
Yum!
Bon appétit!
Congratulations!
Horinishi is the best!
I love the fresh basil!
This is so good!
Yay!
It tastes amazing.
Wow!
This is so good. This is so good.
Yum. Yum. Yum.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
There you go, Mr. Giraudoux.
How is it? It's good.
Oh, yummy!
Wow, I'm so happy.
Wow, it's a few more than I expected.
I'm so happy. I'm so happy.
Yay!
Even if you don't use holinish...
I usually eat it with salt and pepper, but it still tastes so good!
I can't believe you thought of this in middle school... genius!
Genius!
This is Ogawa
Ogawa loves tomatoes!
Delicious!
I used to eat tomatoes and cheese in the microwave.
I used to eat something similar to this?
So it's too much of an upgrade.
This tastes a little amazing.
It's delicious.
Good game. I didn't think it would be this high level.
That's pretty good.
Yay!
Delicious, delicious!
Next, what is the best snack Endo makes?
Natto cheese!
Natto cheese toast!
Natto cheese toast?
I eat it often.
I love natto.
Usually, I like to eat it with white rice.
But this time, I put it on a piece of bread because it's my evening meal.
I eat natto a lot.
Now, let's see, Mr. Himura, Mr. Himura in the kitchen!
Mr. Himura, Mr. Himura
My knee hurts.
Knees!
First of all, butter.
Butter
Or margarine
Only margarine
Anything is fine.
Endo's bangs are rather nicely snapped today.
It's true.
I wonder if it's the same for Mr. Himura.
Oh, my.
They look so similar.
Bangs.
They're the same.
I'm so happy.
We've switched.
You didn't switch?
That's not true.
We didn't switch?
Himura, too. He turned black.
Yes, you've noticed.
I can see it. It's a little darker or bluish.
Yes, it's been a while since I've gone dark, and parted my bangs a bit.
Does it suit you?
It looks good.
It does look good, but with parted bangs.
Come on, Mr. Himura, Mr. Himura.
This way, sir.
Mr. Himura.
Did you change the arrangement of your bangs?
I rearranged it in my room.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I was looking at him and laughing.
He was talking about some weird arrangement.
Natto.
Is this anything?
Anything is fine. I'm not picky.
I'm not particular about it.
That's the way to open it.
I always do it this way.
I usually just take it and put it in Mr. Himura's mouth.
I don't do that.
But, yes, I put all the sauce and mustard in now.
So you make this the usual way.
Did you put it all in?
I already put in everything that comes with it.
Mayonnaise.
And after spreading all the natto on the bread, put a lot of mayonnaise on top.
Horinishi... it's so good!
Horinishi, no way!
Mixed cheese, any kind of cheese, even sliced cheese!
If it's melted, it'll be good!
And while it cooks in the toaster for 3 minutes...
3 minutes!
This time!
Time!
Okay, Mr. Endo.
Who is your favorite menu item?
Southern Ulsters.
Oh, yes!
Yes! Meow!
Southern All Stars.
I was hoping to get Pea to sing a little.
What's your favorite Southern song?
I don't know.
Everybody's song.
Yes, I do.
That's a great way to lead them.
Don't Stop Loving Me
I wish you would tell her the lyrics, Hirora
You keep on walking
Swaying my heart, swaying my heart, swaying my heart
Shaking my thoughts
I'll hold on to you
Anyway, anyway
Anyway, I'll get around you
In a false shirt
To the hesitant buttons
In the flow of time
It's good to sing
Rainbow flowers
Ah, the bells went
It was one bell.
That's good, huh?
Too bad, it was one bell.
It's done.
When you look up, it's done.
Yes, it's done!
Natto cheese toast.
Yes, it's ready!
Then, let's eat!
Bon appétit!
It looks amazing.
Okay, here we go.
Yay!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's good.
It's so good. It's so good. It's so good.
It goes well with the toast.
It's got that natto feeling, too.
Yeah, but it's good.
Oh, it's good.
It's very satisfying.
It's good!
I thought it would be more natto, natto, natto.
I thought it was going to be more natto, natto, natto.
It's a good fusion.
It goes really well with bread.
Yes, it does. Yes, it does, Ogawa.
I want to eat it every day
I know, I know.
If this were a hotel breakfast, you could get 3,000 yen for it.
Well, it's expensive now.
Next, the unknown!
Sugawara will be making a snack.
Healthy tofu chips.
What? Tofu chips?
You want to eat potato chips at night.
But I feel a little guilty about eating them, don't you?
That's when my classmates Naki Inoue and Hiroharu Okuda taught me.
During rehearsals or when we practice late at night
When I was really hungry, I used to make tofu chips.
That's why they're so great, so you don't get fat.
You've got cheese on your chin.
Cheese?
Kimura, cheese on your chin.
Why did you start the show?
I have cheese on my chin.
Well, well, well, Kimura-san in the kitchen, Kimura-san.
Choryuken!
Oh, no! Junior high school kids are here!
Oh, no.
Can I have a piece of tofu?
Yes, sir.
With a spatula?
I'll just crush it with a spatula.
Oh, I'll just crush it.
You're going to crush it all?
I'll smash them all up.
Oh, you're gonna smash it so bad.
I'm gonna smash it so hard.
I'm gonna crush it so much.
I'm gonna crush it so much!
Oh, this is the messy version of messy messy messy.
It's amazing that I'm still hungry enough to make this.
I eat potato chips while I cook.
Don't you ever do that?
It's always the first one.
I did it once.
I've done that.
Yes, I've done it.
I'm sure it's happened.
When do you put the trash in?
What's that?
Garbage?
Shokichi's food tastes like garbage.
You're right... tell him... tell him...
I've graduated from garbage.
You say you've graduated from garbage...
From trash.
I'm out.
Graduated.
I'll get on the train.
It's so provincial when those two do it.
That's for sure.
I wonder why.
I wonder if it gives them a warm, local feeling.
I'm glad.
Ho-kai hokka hokka
Was Shokichi like that?
The way he does it...
His groove is like an old man's...
I'm a little embarrassed because I hid it.
I see.
Yes, in the microwave.
Crushed tofu on a cookie sheet
Spread a thin layer of tofu on the cookie sheet
Microwave for 6 minutes on each side
It takes a lot of work, so here is the finished product
I like to replace it with another one.
Ta-da!
Not so much!
No, it's like this.
It's like this.
Yes, it is!
Add salt and aonori (green laver) to taste.
It's done!
Bon appétit!
I don't know if it's tofu or not.
It's really hard.
Then let's crack it open a little.
Yes.
When did the sound come out?
Let's hear the sound.
The sound is wonderful!
Okay, here we go.
Wait a minute.
You broke it.
It's all over.
It's all over the place.
Oh...
I don't feel guilty.
I don't feel guilty at all. I wonder what it tastes like.
I put too much on it. I like it when you put too much on it.
I recommend it.
Yum! Yum! It's okay!
It's even better when it's freshly made.
It's even better when it's fresh.
It's delicious!
It's like beans for Setsubun, or soybeans after you eat it.
It's indescribably delicious! It's tofu!
It tastes better with more salt.
It's like after eating Setsubun no Beans.
Second time, second time!
After this, Umezawa's little restaurant opens!
Captain Umezawa is the last of the late-night snack club!
What will you make for us, Umezawa?
It doesn't use fire or microwave, so it's really easy!
I'll chop it up.
I'm a tornado fan.
Please stop... the angle of your body is like you're doing it.
The yellow one looks good in a tornado like this.
Yes, yellow is definitely the best color.
The seasonings are a little too much of a nuisance.
The one that's close is bent over... is it bent over or are the plums too big?
No, don't bend over.
Are the plums big?
I'm particular about it.
Kamata's dashi soy sauce.
Oh, this one.
It's famous, but it's the only soy sauce I use.
It's delicious.
Just for about 3 seconds. It's a little too much today.
Okay.
I use Sekine's sesame oil.
You're particular about it.
Is this also delicious?
It's delicious!
Sekine sesame oil!
Then add fish sauce.
Nam pla?
I put fish sauce.
I'm very particular about this.
It gives it a kind of Asian feel, right?
It does!
But it's the flavor of the seafood, so it goes really well with it.
Fish sauce, well, it's definitely fish.
And mix it all together, and it's done.
Is that the end of it?
It's over.
The end.
How many spoons do you eat this with?
It's wrapped in Korean seaweed.
Oh, no!
This means it's done.
Finished!
It's done!
This is so easy.
Oh, which one?
That one.
Yes, Mr. Himura, I'll show you one.
Meruru-shii!
No, no, no.
I didn't request one.
We talked about snacks on the previous episode, and I told him pickled shiso leaves were delicious, so I put some on him.
What? It has nothing to do with this?
No, it has nothing to do with this.
It's something with garlic and soy sauce.
Yes, with soy sauce and dashi.
You can put this on the side for the two of us, if you like.
Thank you.
I want some of that.
You want some? Really?
I'll bring it.
Wait a minute, this is like a little restaurant.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's too rich to eat by itself.
You just eat it as it is?
I'd eat it as it is.
Wow!
So mature!
But it's also delicious wrapped in nori (seaweed) or on top of cheese.
Want some sake?
No, it really goes well with sake.
Sake, please!
Run, run, Age!
So, Umezawa, here's a tasting of the winning tortaque and the extra pickled shiso leaves!
Bon appétit!
Then wrap this up!
Oh no, what should I do?
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It's different.
Is it because of the fish sauce?
A little bit of fish sauce.
Aroma
It mellows it out.
Maybe.
Yum!
Sad!
The Korean seaweed and fish sauce... it's not the Torotaku I know.
The kind I don't know.
Delicious!
I want to add more fish sauce!
The shiso leaves are so thick!
Let's eat shiso leaves!
It's really thick!
Yum!
The shiso leaves are even better than I imagined!
Of course, you can taste the herbaceous shiso leaves.
The garlic soy sauce and these hawk's claws are so good!
It's so good!
Rice goes great with it too!
Ah!
That's why I put it on
This is for Nishino.
You're so mature.
No, this is mature.
I love this kind of thing.
I'm a little confused... how do you choose?
It's delicious
This is what we did today.
Here you go.
Good girl!
But Kubo made dumplings, too.
Good woman!
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, interest rates...
So, a few simple late-night snacks
A little bit of raw
Two votes for Kubo, three for Ume!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I wanted to, sure Kubo I was lost, lost, lost, but the Forest of Willingness actually had all these levels pretty much the whole time before
I'm really a champion, I knew it!
I was wondering how it would turn out since I like austere Japanese food, so I'm glad to hear that!
I'm glad you enjoyed the live catering and the food.
Next time, I'll be talking about the food at the top of the food truck at midnight!
I'm Sakura Endo.
I'm curling my hair.
How do you like it?
Please subscribe to our channel!
Bye bye!